# Yu Long Hang, Matthew

(852) 93472961 | longhangyu0809@gmail.com

https://longhangyu-matthew.github.io/react-portfolio

Available to start work immediately

Web and Shopify developer with 2 years of experience in helping local and multinational brands develop and maintain e-commerce websites. Proven experience in creating brand pages and email templates using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Liquid. A collaborative communicator who is able to multitask effectively in a timely manner.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Assistant Training Officer**

MAR 2023 - AUG 2023

# Intelligent Software Co., Ltd.

- Conducted STEM product research to compare and choose the most suitable products for teaching purposes
- Created 4 course materials for tutors to teach secondary school students in STEM extracurricular activities
- Designed 5 drone shows for primary and secondary schools to celebrate their anniversaries
- Developed good presentation skills through conducting product research and outlining course content

## **Web Developer**

**SEPT 2021 - FEB 2023** 

#### **5 Miles Lab Company Limited**

- A digital advertising agency performs online advertising campaigns for clients through various digital channels
- Developed and maintained 6 e-commerce websites for local and multinational brands using Shopify, including Meyer and Pots & Pans, to ensure clients' unique needs are met
- Collaborated with designers to translate designs and wireframes into code using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap,
  JavaScript and jQuery
- Developed over 10 festive and brand pages using Shopify Liquid and Shogun to help clients generate new revenue streams
- Created over 20 email marketing templates using Klaviyo, Mailjet, and MailChimp and collected customer email addresses for better Customer Relationship Management
- Developed good communication skills with clients by understanding their needs and suggesting possible solutions

# Web Designer (Intern)

JUL 2019 - AUG 2019

#### **Sino Computer Service Limited**

- Designed, developed, and maintained the company's website from start to finish using the Concrete5
  Content Management System
- Developed good data organizing skills through managing and categorizing content using CMS

## OTHER EXPERIENCE

#### **Volunteer Content Creator & Reviewer**

JUN 2015 - PRESENT

## Online rhythm game with over 20 million registered users

- Lead and manage a team of over 50 quality assurance members to provide high-quality content to the player base
- Evaluate quality assurance members regularly to ensure they meet performance standards

Designer AUG 2019 – FEB 2020

Publicity and Publication Affairs Committee, Executive Committee, The 26th Session of The Hong Kong Polytechnic University Students' Union

- Designed graphics for the union's social media platforms, including Facebook and Instagram
- Developed good Adobe skills by designing digital content using Photoshop and Illustrator

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science in Internet and Multimedia Technologies**

2016 - 2020

The Hong Kong Polytechnic University

# **SKILLS**

Web Development Proficient in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript and jQuery

Intermediate in PHP Junior in ReactJS

**E-commerce** Proficient in Shopify

**CRM & Automation** Proficient in Klaviyo, Mailjet and MailChimp

**Design & Creative** Proficient in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro and Canva

**Game Engine** Intermediate in Unity

**3D Modeling** Intermediate in Autodesk 3DS MAX and Blender

**Office Applications** Proficient in MS Word, Excel and PowerPoint

**Language** Native in Cantonese

Fluent in spoken and written English and Mandarin